(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Cook it!
Go!
F-U-B-U-K-I
M-I-O
Okay!
K-O-R-O-N-E
Are you ready?
Go!
O-K-A-Y-U
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while for the performance to begin.
公演ハッシュタグ #超ゲマズ_day1
Performance Hashtag #SuperGamers_day1
(ミオ)
(Mio)
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
(おかゆ)
(Okayu)
(ころね)
(Korone)
(ミオ)
(Mio)
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
Are you ready?
Perfect!
(フブキ)
(Fubuki)
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
こーん！とキツネが登場
"Kon!" A fox makes her appearance
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
I'm the white-haired, fluffy-eared Shirakami Fubuki
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
It won't start if you're holding back
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukonbu club too
Hi Friends!! (Yeah!!)
古今東西 コーン茶をちょーだい
From all times and places, give me corn tea
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
I'm not an AI, my specialty is being an MC
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
I prefer golden carp over red love
うちうちうち
Internal, internal, internal
We are gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
はーい！とお呼びでミオ
"Hi!" You called for Mio
みんなを眺めるお母さん
I'm the mother watching over everyone
おなかがすいたら うちにおいで
If you're hungry, come over to my place
ご飯は炊きたて ウチの子一番
The rice is freshly cooked, my kids are the best
みぉーん！ (みぉーん！)
Mio-n! (Mio-n!)
今日も元気に おはみおーん
Good morning Mio-n with energy again today
タロット占いで 導いてあげる
I'll guide you with a tarot reading
お神輿わっしょい どこまでも
Heave-ho the portable shrine, anywhere we go
うちうちうち
Internal, internal, internal
We are gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
もぐもぐおかゆだよ
Mogu mogu, it's Okayu
全人類を 誘惑しちゃう
I'll seduce all of humanity
おにぎり食べたら ほっこり笑顔
Eat an onigiri and you'll have a warm smile
今日はどんなイタズラ しようかな
I wonder what kind of prank I'll play today
もぐもぐ (おかゆー！)
Mogu mogu (Okayu!)
全力投球 どんとこい
Giving it my all, bring it on
甘い誘惑 おまかせあれ
Leave the sweet temptations to me
全肯定で 愛してね
Love me with total affirmation
うちうちうち
Internal, internal, internal
We are gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
ゆびゆび！ころねだよ
Yubi yubi! It's Korone
パン屋の看板 振り回せ
Swinging around the bakery sign
骨をしゃぶれば 幸せいっぱい
Sucking on bones brings lots of happiness
戌神ころねが 守ってあげる
Inugami Korone will protect you
ゆびゆび！ (ゆびゆび！)
Yubi yubi! (Yubi yubi!)
今日も元気に 1! 2! 3!
Energy today too, 1! 2! 3!
レトロゲームも 大好きだよ
I love retro games too
愛の鞭なら 痛くない
If it's a whip of love, it doesn't hurt
うちうちうち
Internal, internal, internal
We are gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
All Ready?
フブキ！
Fubuki!
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
おかゆ！
Okayu!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
We are gamers
おかゆ！
Okayu!
#ゲーマーズ_day1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
#Gamers_Day1
Please wait a moment for the show to start
コロネ
Korone
Ready?
Perfect
クッキキ
Kukkiki
ミオ
Mio
おかゆ
Okayu
コロネ
Korone
hololive GAMERS fes. 超超超超ゲーマーズ
hololive GAMERS fes. Super Super Super Super Gamers
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the show begins.
いくぞー！
Here we go!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
hololive GAMERS!
フブキもやるぞー！
Fubuki's gonna do it too!
ミオも楽しみだよー！
Mio is excited too!
We are GAMERS!
みんな待ってたー？
Did everyone wait?
いっぱい楽しんでいこうね！
Let's have lots of fun!
We are GAMERS!
フブニャン！
Fubu-nyan!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox appears,
白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
white-haired furry-eared Shirakami Fubuki here!
スッ込んでちゃ始まらない
It won't start if you stay inside,
君もすこん部に入部しなさい
you should join the Sukon Club too!
Hi Friends!! (Yeah!!) Hi Friends!! (Yeah!!)
古今東西 コーン茶をちょーだい
From all ages and places, give me some corn tea!
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
I'm not an AI, my specialty is MC-ing,
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
I prefer the golden carp over red love!
We are GAMERS!
ミオしゃー！
Mio-sha!
ウチウチウチだよ大神ミオだよ
It's Uchi-uchi-uchi, it's Ookami Mio,
黒髪ケモミミ大神ミオ
black-haired furry-eared Ookami Mio!
スッ込んでご免あそばせ
Excuse me for staying inside,
ライ様もお笑い出したら止まらないゲラゲラ
even Rai-sama can't stop laughing, gera-gera!
つまりフフはホッホト
In short, Fufu is Ho-hoto,
破壊せず召し上がれ オゥホゥホゥ
enjoy without destroying it, Oh-ho-ho!
タロット占いで視る未来
A future seen through tarot readings,
ホラーゲームやりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えば
When the four of us are together...
ゲーマーズ最強！
GAMERS are the strongest!
君も遊ぼう ピース出して
You play too, show your peace sign!
瞳凝らしてレベル上げて
Focus your eyes and level up,
今日は何をプレイしよう
what shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃうぜ
I'll even conquer your heart,
セーブをしてシミュレーション
save and simulate!
初見も古参も大歓迎よ
First-timers and veterans are all welcome,
そう 2nd Gameは楽しむね！
yes, let's enjoy the 2nd Game!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS
おかゆー！
Okayu!
もぐもぐもぐもぐおにぎりおかゆ
Mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu, Onigiri Okayu,
おにぎりおにぎりハイ！どうぞ
Onigiri onigiri, here! You go.
キラキラフラフラ招き猫だもん
Sparkling and wandering, I'm a maneki-neko,
ほら そっちのがよくない？
look, isn't that better?
まったりゆっくり奏でるリズム
A rhythm played calmly and slowly,
全肯定するどこがいい？
I'll fully affirm you, what's good about it?
全肯定降臨オッケー！
Fully affirming descent, okay!
毎日ポカポカいい感じさ
Every day feels warm and good.
ころねー！
Korone!
おあよう指指わおわお
Ohayo, fingers fingers, wao wao,
パンをコネコネ戌神ころね
kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
原宿なまりキン消しチャーム
Harajuku accent, Kinkeshi charm,
スーパーNEETな僕だけど熱燗系
I'm a super NEET but I'm the hot sake type!
止まらぬイントネーション 割れるリアクション
Unstoppable intonation, cracking reaction,
まずは指を捧げてくれる？
first, will you offer your fingers?
配信中 ボコッたな骨してオッケー！
Broadcasting, okay to smash bones!
こぶつのレトロゲーお届け
Delivering Kobutsu's retro games.
4人揃えば
When the four of us are together...
ゲーマーズ最強！
GAMERS are the strongest!
フラグ立てれば即回収
If a flag is set, it's immediately collected!
腕を磨いて狙い撃ち
Hone your skills and aim,
今日は何をプレイしよう
what shall we play today?
君のハートをキャプチャしちゃうぜ
I'll capture your heart,
ワクワクするこの感情
this exciting feeling!
第9形態はやめらんない
Can't stop at the 9th form,
だって ゲームが好きなんだもん
because I love games!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジのお時間です！
Suddenly, it's Bonus Challenge time!
大きな声でレスポンスをして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Let's aim for a high score by responding loudly!
Are you ready?
せーの！こーんこーん！
One, two! Kon kon!
こーんこーん！
Kon kon!
にょんにょん！
Nyon nyon!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
こーんこーん！
Kon kon!
にょんにょん！
Nyon nyon!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
おおー！
Ohhh!
4人揃えば
When the four of us are together...
ゲーマーズ最強！
GAMERS are the strongest!
上手くいかなくても再プレイ
Even if it doesn't go well, play again!
ギブアップなんて諦めない
I won't give up by giving up,
エンディングは見に行こう
let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃうぜ
I'll even conquer your heart,
セーブをしてシミュレーション
save and simulate!
初見も古参も大歓迎よ
First-timers and veterans are all welcome,
そう 2nd Gameは楽しむね！
yes, let's enjoy the 2nd Game!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS
こうして、さいたまスーパーアリーナに平和が訪れたのであった！
And so, peace returned to Saitama Super Arena!
We are Gamers!
はい！ということで始まりましたー！
Alright! And so, it begins!
いや、すごいね！ホロライブゲーマーズフェス
超！超！超！超！ゲーマーズ2です！
Isn't it amazing! It's Hololive Gamers Fes:
Super! Super! Super! Super! Gamers 2!
はい、じゃあちょっと自己紹介やっていきますかね。
Alright, shall we do some self-introductions?
はい、皆さん！こんこんきーつね！
Alright, everyone! Kon-kon-kitsune!
こんこんきーつね！
Kon-kon-kitsune!
はい、白上フブキです。よろしくお願いします！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki. Please take care of me!
そしてそして、1曲目ちょっとね、
『We are Gamers』やらせてもらったんですけども...
And also, for our first song,
we performed 'We are Gamers'...
ついにね、4人ということで、
いるじゃないですか、赤いのか！さあ！さあ！
Finally, with the four of us...
there she is, the red one! Come on! Come on!
はい！大神ミオ... うち！うち！うちだよ！
Yes! Ookami Mio... It's me! It's me! It's me!
大神ミオだよー... あ、違う！
It's Ookami Mio... oh, wait, that's wrong!
おっかみみおの皆さんいらっしゃいませ！だよね！
Welcome to all the Ookami-mio fans! That's it!
おかしいんだよな...
Something's not right...
続いて！はい！はい！
Next! Yes! Yes!
もぐもぐ... おかゆー！
Munch munch... Okayu!
はい、どうも！猫又おかゆです！
Yes, hello! I'm Nekomata Okayu!
今日はね、最高の思い出を作って、楽しんじゃいましょう！
Today, let's make the best memories and have some fun!
はい、そして！
Yes! And!
はい、ゆー！
Yes, fin-!
びー！
Gers!
ゆびゆびー！戌神ころねです！
Yubi-yubi! I'm Inugami Korone!
みんな今日は大事な日なの。何の日か知ってる？
Everyone, today is an important day. Do you know what day it is?
今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日！
Today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
ということで戌神ころねです、よろしくお願いします！
And so, I'm Inugami Korone, nice to meet you!
ということでね、改めて、4人揃っても、初めての！
And so, once again, the four of us together for the first time!
ホロライブゲーマーズフェス超！超！超！超！ゲーマーズ2、
そのDay 1がここ、さいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕でございます！
Hololive Gamers Fes: Super! Super! Super! Super! Gamers 2!
Day 1 is here at Saitama Super Arena, now open!
大きい！なんとですね、あのDay 1、Day 2、
両日とも完売ということで！
Huge! Surprisingly, both Day 1 and Day 2
are completely sold out!
ええー！すごい！
Eeeh! Amazing!
なんで、Day 1、Day 2ともに、約1万... 5千とか
7千とかのファンの皆さんが今日来てくださってる。そうです！
So, for both Day 1 and Day 2, about 15,000 to
17,000 fans are here today. That's right!
運営さんから、Day 1、Day 2合わせて3.5万人くらいだそうです。
Management said that between Day 1 and Day 2, it's about 35,000 people.
はー！すごすぎる！
Haa! That's incredible!
なんでそんなにいるの？すごいね。
Why are there so many? Amazing.
ほぼ人間じゃん。
They're almost all humans.
いらっしゃいますね、本当に？
Are they really there? Honestly?
ほぼ人間だよ。人間以外入ってないだろう。
They're almost all humans. There shouldn't be anyone but humans here.
昨年はね、あの国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども、
今回はさいたまスーパーアリーナということで。すごいですよね、本当に。
Last year was at the National Yoyogi Stadium First Gymnasium,
but this time it's Saitama Super Arena. It's really amazing.
さて改めてこのイベントはですね、ゲームが大好きな我々ゲーマーズを中心に、
超超超超豪華なゲストと一緒に...
Now, once again, this event is centered around us Gamers who love games,
along with super, super, super, super gorgeous guests...
色々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けする、
プレミアムイベントです！
Challenging various game titles and delivering live performances,
it's a premium event!
しかも今回皆さんに、あの突然出てきて「え、3Dだの？」って感じなんですけど、
4人のお揃いの衣装、お披露目でございます！
Plus, we suddenly appeared and you might be like "Wait, 3D?",
but we're debuting our matching outfits for the four of us!
可愛いー！かわちいー！
Cute! So cute!
いやね、本当この衣装可愛いから着たいねって言ってたら、
用意してくださいました。ありがとうございます！
Well, we were saying how cute these outfits are and how we wanted to wear them,
and they prepared them for us. Thank you very much!
夢のようだよね。
It's like a dream.
本当本当、可愛いですよね。
Really, really, they're cute, aren't they?
さらにですね、会場では一部撮影OKなパートがありますので、
そちらでは是非ね、スマホでお写真を撮っていただけると嬉しいです。
Furthermore, there's a part of the venue where photography is allowed,
so please do take pictures with your smartphones there.
ということでね、始まっていくんですけども、
一人ずつちょっと意気込みお願いしたいと思いますよ。じゃあまずは、ミオから！
And so, we're getting started, but I'd like to ask each of you
for your enthusiasm. First up, Mio!
はい！え、今年は... 去年はね、ちょっとお休みしちゃったんですけど...
Yes! Well, this year... last year, I had to take a break...
去年は私、出られなかったんですけど、今年は4人でね、無事に開催することができたので。
I couldn't make it last year, but this year, we were able to hold the event with all four of us.
えー、明日も無事に終えられるように、
Um, so that we can finish tomorrow safely as well,
体調管理だけはしっかりして、2日間過ごしたいと思います！頑張るぞー！
I'll make sure to take good care of my health and spend these two days well! I'll do my best!
頑張るぞー！おー！
We'll do our best! Yeah!
はい！ではでは、続いてはおかゆ！
Alright! Now then, next is Okayu!
はーい！ま、僕はね、あの、去年に引き続きの参加となるんですが、
Heeey! Well, for me, it's my second year in a row participating, but,
ま、今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日ということでね。
well, today is Shohei Ohtani's birthday, you see.
待って待って、大谷はいないのよ！
Wait, wait, Ohtani isn't here!
おおー、すごい人だけどさ、
Ooh, he's an amazing guy, but...
なので、ギャグ打率3割、
So, with a gag batting average of .300,
目指して頑張りたいと思います！ちょっと、あっためてください！
I'll do my best to aim for that! Please, warm up for me!
ギャグだけでさ、おかゆならもっといけそうだけどね。
Just with gags, Okayu could probably do even better.
いやいやいや。
No, no, no.
そして！
And next!
はい！今日はね、翔平に素敵な感動をプレゼント、
Yes! Today, I'll deliver a wonderful moving feeling to Shohei,
届けられるように、頑張るぞー！
as a present, I'll do my best!
翔平に！？せめてコロネスキーに届けてくれよ！
To Shohei!? At least deliver it to the Koronesukis!
コロネスキーに届けまーす！
I'll deliver it to the Koronesukis!
えー、そしてそして。
Um, and then, and then.
はい、白上はですね、皆さん、あの、昨年に引き続きまして、
Yes, as for Shirakami, everyone, um, continuing from last year,
なんと、あの台本の、あの8割が白上が読み上げるということで、
amazingly, Shirakami will be reading about 80% of the script,
あの、1日目、2日目合わせて、喉に気をつけつつ、
so, over Day 1 and Day 2, while being careful with my throat,
かすれ始めたら、「あ、頑張ってるな」と思って、
if my voice starts getting husky, please think 'Ah, she's working hard,'
いっぱいサイリウム振ってください！よろしくお願いします！
and wave lots of penlights! Thank you!
お前らの声には負けねえから！よろしく！
I won't lose to your voices! Best regards!
はい！そしてですね、今日と明日行われる「超ゲマズ2」は、
Alright! And then, 'Chō Gamers 2' taking place today and tomorrow,
ABEMA Pay-Per-Viewで生配信してます！
is being streamed live on ABEMA Pay-Per-View!
見てるー？見てるー？
Are you watching? Are you watching?
見てるよー！
They're watching!
コメントもね、我々見えておりますよ。
We can see your comments too.
ねえ、ありがとうございます。
Yeah, thank you very much.
こちら、配信チケットは絶賛発売中です。
Streaming tickets are now on sale to great acclaim.
イベントが終わっても、8月4日、月曜日の23時59分まで、
Even after the event ends, until 11:59 PM on Monday, August 4th,
何度でも見返すことができます！
you can rewatch it as many times as you like!
購入特典としましては、Day 1とDay 2で異なるシチュエーションの、
As for purchase benefits, we have Day 1 and Day 2 with different situations,
限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます。
exclusive original voice dramas included.
Day 1は「秘密の事前プロデュースボイス」。
Day 1 is 'Secret Pre-performance Produced Voice'.
秘密！？エッチなやつ！？
Secret!? Is it something naughty!?
違います！そしてDay 2は、
No, it's not! And Day 2 is,
「内緒の超ゲマズ お疲れ様ボイス」。
'Secret Super Gamers Otsukaresama Voice'.
これ、エッチなやつかな！？
Is this a naughty one!?
エッチじゃないです！聴いてください！
It's not naughty! Please listen to it!
あとはですね、我々の直筆メッセージ入りの、
Also, there are live photos with our handwritten messages,
ライブ画像もついてきますので、ぜひチェックしてください！
included, so please be sure to check them out!
昨年行われました「超ゲマズ」のダイジェストが、
A digest of last year's 'Chō Gamers' event,
ABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
is currently available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年もね、めちゃめちゃ面白かったので、ぜひとも見てください！
Last year was really fun too, so please take a look!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
さらにさらに、イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始します！
And furthermore, mail-order sales for merchandise will start after the event!
ありがたいことに、Day 1のグッズが完売らしいです！
Gratefully, it seems Day 1 merchandise has sold out!
すごーい！ありがとうございます！
Amazing! Thank you everyone!
グッズの受注販売は、本日の朝10時から、
Mail-order sales for goods are from 10:00 AM today,
7月21日の23時59分まで、
until 11:59 PM on July 21st,
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中でございます。
available at the Cyber Goods Store.
こちらのグッズ、9月下旬までにはお届け予定とのことです。
These goods are scheduled to be delivered by late September.
えー、そしてなんと！
Um, and amazingly!
事後限定グッズとして、アクリルパネルが追加されます！
Acrylic panels will be added as mail-order exclusive goods!
イベント限定グッズが手に入る最後のチャンスなので、
This is your last chance to get event-exclusive goods,
ぜひぜひこちらチェックしてください！
so please, please check this out!
なんか話を聞けない生徒みたいになってます。
It's like you're students who won't listen.
ほらー、ちゃんと聞いてよ！混ざっちゃって, もう。
Look, listen properly! You're all mixed up, geez.
じゃあ、先生お話しするからね。
Now, the teacher is going to speak.
さらにさらに、もうご存じの方もいらっしゃると思いますが、
And furthermore, as some of you may already know,
NTTドコモさんの「home 5G」と、
a collaboration with NTT Docomo's 'home 5G',
コラボが決定しました！
has been confirmed!
先生の話は聞かなくてもいいけど、声は出さないで。
You don't have to listen to the teacher, but don't make noise.
ごめんなさーい！
Sorry!
NTTドコモさんのご紹介してたでしょう！？
I was introducing NTT Docomo, wasn't I!?
すみませーん！
Sorry!
お友達か！
Are we friends or something!?
お友達よ！
We are friends!
じゃあ入口でもらえるうちわ、皆さんゲットしましたか？
So, did everyone get the fans given at the entrance?
もらった方ー！
Those who got one!
おおー！ありがとうございまーす！
Ooh! Thank you very much!
もらったうちわも使って、熱中症対策万全にして
Use the fans you received to take full precautions against heatstroke...
わー最後まで、お楽しみください！
And enjoy the show until the very end!
めちゃくちゃ、いいですね
That's really nice.
ちょっともう一回ゆっくり、いじってもいいですか？
Can I play around with it slowly once more?
まだまだ続きますよ！
There's still more to come!
我々ゲマズを応援したいっていう声が多かったので、今回 CheerSPOT さんとコラボすることになりました！
Since many wanted to support us Gamers, we're collaborating with CheerSPOT for this event!
誰でも簡単に好きな CheerSPOT の場所に白上たちゲーマーズの応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily place support ads for Shirakami and the Gamers at their favorite CheerSPOT locations!
これすごい！
This is amazing!
会場内もねこれあのなんとねスポットが我々になってまして、びっくりしました
Even inside the venue, the spots have become us! I was surprised.
そうなの？
Is that so?
見てたよ！ありがたかったね、パネルのやつか
I saw it! We're so grateful for the panel displays.
そうそうそうそう
Right, right, right, right.
めちゃくちゃ、可愛かったですね
They were really cute.
そしてさらに、さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初披露！
And furthermore, life-size figures will be unveiled at Saitama Super Arena!
3月の EXPO 会場で発表されましたフブミオ等身大に続きまして
Following the Fubuki and Mio life-size figures announced at the EXPO in March...
おかころのフィギュアも発売予定揃って発表されましたー！
The Okayu and Korone figures were also announced for release together!
やったー！
Hooray!
よかったー！配信ではさ、なかったらおかにゃんと毛玉なんじゃないかって言ってたんですけど、ちゃんと揃ってました
Thank goodness! On stream, we joked it might just be Okayu and a furball, but they were both there!
よかったー
Thank goodness.
めちゃくちゃ、可愛かったです
They were really cute.
そしてまた本日から新作のフィギュアがデザインここから受注開始です！
And starting today, pre-orders for the new figure designs begin right here!
可愛いー！
So cute!
8月7日までにコトブキヤストアで予約してくれた方には特典のステッカーをプレゼントされるそうです！
Pre-order at the Kotobukiya Store by August 7th to receive a bonus sticker!
可愛すぎるー！
Too cute!
白上とミオも欲しいなという風に思った、そこのあなた！あなた！あなた！
For those who thought "I want Fubuki and Mio too!" You! You! You!
お！
Oh!
超ゲマズ2の開催を記念して、期間限定でフブミオ追加予約を開始じゃー！
To celebrate Super Gamers 2, additional pre-orders for Fubumi-Mio start now!
やったー！
Hooray!
逃したよーっていうのもね、何人か X で見かけましたので、これを機に是非ともご予約お願いします
I saw several people on X saying they missed out, so please take this chance to pre-order!
最後にカンフル様による協賛企業グッズ、超ポップコーンと超グリルチキンのご紹介でございます！
Finally, introducing sponsored goods from Canfull: Super Popcorn and Super Grilled Chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなってるとのことです
The designs feature the key visual of this event prominently.
ポップコーンは税込1000円で、缶詰は税込1500円での販売でございます
Popcorn is 1,000 yen and canned food is 1,500 yen, both including tax.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、缶詰はグリルチキン味になってます
The flavors are Salt Caramel for the popcorn and Grilled Chicken for the canned food.
トレカも付いてる！
It even comes with a trading card!
こちらのグッズは数量限定商品のため、お急ぎください！
These items are limited edition, so please hurry!
集合アクリルパネルも含めて、事後でしか購入できないグッズですので、皆さん是非確認してください
These items, including the group acrylic panel, are only available after the event. Please check them out!
なんと！なんと！ちなみに今回韓国でライブビューイングもやってるそうです！
Wow! Wow! By the way, we're also doing a live viewing in Korea!
お！韓国の皆さん、アンニョンハセヨ！
Oh! Everyone in Korea, annyeonghaseyo!
アンニョンハセヨ！
Annyeonghaseyo!
見てる？ありがとー！
Are you watching? Thank you!
色々ご紹介も終わりましたので、早速最初に行うゲームタイトルを発表しちゃいましょう！
Now that the introductions are over, let's announce the title of the first game we'll play!
おお！始まる？
Oh! Is it starting?
いきますよ！せーの、こちら！
Here we go! One, two, this one!
ビビッター！
BIBITTAR!
イエーイ！
Yay!
こちら、ルールは超簡単
The rules for this one are super simple.
ミニゲームに対し、タイミングよくボタンを押して、ギリギリで止めるだけ
For each mini-game, just press the button with good timing and stop at the very last second.
はい、我々の度胸を試す究極のビビリチェッカーゲームとなっております
Yes, it's the ultimate chicken-checker game to test our courage.
よりギリギリを攻めると、Cool の称号がもらえるそうです
If you push it closer to the limit, you'll receive the "Cool" title.
今回ですね、我々個人戦でございます
This time, we're doing a free-for-all.
1つのミニゲームに対して2人がそれぞれ挑戦します
Two people will challenge each mini-game individually.
様々な組み合わせで合計6ゲーム行わせていただきたいと思います
We'll be playing a total of 6 games with various combinations.
我々の Cool の合計数で1位を決めたいと思いますので、よろしくお願いします
The winner will be determined by the total number of "Cools," so look forward to it!
ゲームを始める前に、なんと今回巨大コントローラーを用意してくれたということで
Before we start, apparently they've prepared a giant controller for us!
はい、召喚しましょう！これでちょっと会場の皆さんも一緒に
Yes, let's summon it! Everyone in the venue, please join us too.
「いでよ、巨大コントローラー」って叫んでくれると嬉しいです、できますか？
I'd love it if you could all shout, "Come forth, giant controller!" Can you do it?
おーい！
Ohey!
巨大コントローラーに…
To the giant controller...
ここに来ますからね、皆さん行きますよ！
It's coming here, everyone, are you ready?!
せーの！
Ready, set...!
いでよ！巨大コントローラー！！
Come forth! Giant Controller!!
おおー！出たー！！
Whoa! It's here!!
出た出た！
It's out, it's out!
すごい！大きいね！
Wow! It's huge!
すごい、ちゃんと我々のマークになっている。
Amazing, it even has our icons on it.
かわいいー！
So cute!
では、どの順番でチャレンジしていきますか？
Now then, in what order should we take the challenge?
我こそはというの。
Anyone want to go first?
ええー… 我こそはか…
Ehhh... "Anyone want to go first"...
じゃ、でもミオしゃじゃない？やっぱり。
Well, shouldn't it be Miosha? After all.
え！？お帰り！
What?! Welcome back!
そうだよ、ミオしゃお帰り！
That's right, welcome back Miosha!
やったほうがいいって！やったー！ミオしゃー！
You should do it! Yay! Miosha!
じゃ、まずはミオで。続いてはどうする？
Okay, first is Mio. Who's next?
二人目。
Second person.
やりたい！やりたい！
I want to! I want to!
おかゆ二番目。
Okayu is second.
ええー！？
Ehhh?!
おかゆ二番目。
Okayu is second.
おかゆ二番目。流れ的にね。
Okayu is second. Following the flow.
三番目はどうする？
What about the third?
これどっちが三よ。
Which of you is third?
いや、トリは嫌だ。
No, I don't want to be the closer.
三番手。
Third place.
じゃあそういうことでお願いします。
Well then, I'll take that spot.
すごい自由な仕切りだな。
What a free-spirited arrangement.
ということで対戦としまして一番最初はミオおかゆ。
So, the first matchup will be Mio vs. Okayu.
はい！ミオとおかゆが対戦になります。
Yes! It'll be a match between Mio and Okayu.
おおー！
Whoa!
順番で。ねこしゃ、本番やっていきましょう。
In order. Nekosha, let's start for real.
ミオしゃさ、僕が勝っても泣かないでね。
Miosha, don't cry even if I win, okay?
おかゆには何度も負かされてきてるし。
I've been beaten by Okayu so many times...
この猫、めちゃくちゃミニゲーム系強いんですよ。
This cat is incredibly strong at mini-games.
そうだね、ちょっと強いよね。
That's true, she's a bit strong.
強すぎるまである。
She's almost too strong.
このゲームは初見だからさ。
But this is my first time playing this game.
そうだよ、初めてやるよ。
That's right, it's the first time.
適性が高すぎんだってミニゲームの。
Your aptitude for mini-games is just too high.
確かにそれはあるかも。
True, that might be the case.
だからね、そこでうちが勝ったらめっちゃ奇跡的でしょ？
So, if I win there, it'll be a total miracle, right?
奇跡起こしちゃおう！いいよー！
Let's make a miracle happen! Nice!
それではやっていきますか。
Shall we get started then?
はーい！
Yeah!
今から色々ゲームがあるんですけど、まずは「試練の2」を。
We have various games, but first up is "Trial 2".
やっていこうかなと思います。
I think we'll go with that.
これ、多分スタッフさんがやったんですけど、スタッフさんが強すぎる。
A staff member probably did this, but they were too strong.
確かに。若干そんな感じはするんですけど。
True. I get that feeling a bit.
では、準備いいですか、ミオ。
Well, are you ready, Mio?
はーい！頑張るよー！応援しててねー！
Yes! I'll do my best! Please cheer for me!
あちらのお客様から、グラスを滑らせろ。
From that guest over there, slide the glass.
ほうほう、ダンディーなやつね。
Ho ho, a dandy one.
マスター、あちらの美しい女性にこれを。
Master, give this to the beautiful lady over there.
なるほどね。
I see.
かしこまりました。
Understood.
何だこいつの顔。
What's with this guy's face?
かしこまりました。
Understood.
じゃ、クリックすると。
Okay, so if you click...
まず練習ですか。
Is this practice first?
練習ね、はい。グラスを滑らせろ。
Practice, right. Slide the glass.
クリックしてやってみたいと思います。
I'll try clicking it.
左にゲージがある。どうやら長押しして貯めるらしい。
There's a gauge on the left. You hold it down to fill it.
ここか！
Here?!
おおー！？
Whoa?!
おー！
Whoa!
本番行きます。
Going for the real thing.
ここだ！
Here!
おおー！行った！？おめでとう！
Whoa! It went?! Congratulations!
すごーい！！
Amazing!!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
何そのポーズｗ
What's with that pose? lol
真ん中でやりなよ、ミオしゃ。
Do it in the center, Miosha.
まだおかゆの番だから。
It's still Okayu's turn.
そっかそっか、そうだね。
Right, right, you're right.
まだ途中だもんね。
It's still in the middle.
ということでミオが今50だったかな？
So, Mio's score was 50 just now?
50だよ！50！
It's 50! 50!
続いてはおかゆなんですけども、どうですか。
Next up is Okayu, how are you feeling?
行けますか？自信あり？
Can you do it? Confident?
頑張りまーす！
I'll do my best!
頑張ってー！それでは行きますよ、おかゆのスタート！
Good luck! Here we go, Okayu's start!
さて、おかゆも練習があります。
Now, Okayu also has a practice.
練習あるの優しいね。
Practice is so kind.
よーし。
Alright.
行けるか？
Can I do it?
ええー！？
Ehhh?!
お前自分の注文じゃねえかそれ。
That's your own order, isn't it?!
やばい、本番になっちゃった。
Oh no, it's the real thing now.
本番だよ、頑張れ！
It's the real thing, good luck!
行け行け！危ない！
Go, go! Look out!
なんてことですか！
What was that?!
ミオしゃー！
Mio-sha!
そんなお尻フリフリしてさ〜
Doing that butt-shaking dance...
勝ってないんだからね！
you didn't even win!
これで勝てませんか ね？ 今の。
Can't we win with that? Just now.
怠慢！
Slacker!
怠慢じゃないだろ！怠慢じゃないだろ！
I'm not slacking! I'm not slacking!
ミオちゃん強かった〜
Mio-chan was strong~
難しそうだね、これね。
This looks difficult, doesn't it?
や〜ね〜、嘘〜
Right? No way.
ということで皆さん、こちら突然ではございますが...
So everyone, this is sudden, but...
お知らせでございます！
we have an announcement!
なんと、無料配信をご覧の皆様は、ここまでとなります！
The free stream will end here for those watching!
ええええ！！
Eeeeeee!!
続きをご覧になりたい方はぜひ、ABEMA PPVにて...
If you'd like to see the rest, please...
チケットの購入お願いします！
purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
お願いします！
Please do!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
あっさり！バイバイだな！
So quick! It's bye-bye time!
ねえ、これからもね、めちゃくちゃ楽しいゲーム...
You know, from here on, we have some fun games...
ゲストもいるので、楽しんでいただければと思います！
and guests too, so we hope you'll enjoy it!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
見に来てね！
Come watch us!
まったね〜！バイバイ！
See ya! Bye-bye!
バイバイ！ウー！
Bye-bye! Woo!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
Full show available on ABEMA PPV!
ヘい！
Hey!
腑抜けた心に I need you
I need you in my gutless heart
噂のアルカロイド
A rumored alkaloid
あだなはネットの髑髏
My nickname is the net's skull
かき鳴らせディストーション
Let the distortion ring out
付け焼き刃の音
The sound of a makeshift blade
「1, 2, 3, fakkyu」
(1, 2, 3, f*ck you)
行き場を失くしたまま 踊り狂って
Lost and without a place to go, I dance like mad
惨々、笑われたって 死にはしない
No matter how much they laugh at my misery, I won't die
あーだこーだ言わんで 欲しい
I want you to stop with the 'this and that'
僕の心はエゴロック
My heart is an Ego Rock
斜め四十五度、ナンセンス
Forty-five degrees diagonal, nonsense
ノウハウかじって
Biting into the know-how
マンネリを明日に バイバイバイ
And saying bye-bye-bye to the rut of tomorrow
媚びへつらうその姿
That fawning attitude of yours
吐き気の空模様
Makes the sky look nauseating
シニカルな視線の雨
A rain of cynical stares
今日も両目を塞ぐふり
Today I'll pretend to cover my eyes again
僕の心はエゴロック
My heart is an Ego Rock
斜め四十五度、ナンセンス
Forty-five degrees diagonal, nonsense
ノウハウかじって
Biting into the know-how
マンネリを明日に バイバイバイ
And saying bye-bye-bye to the rut of tomorrow
ヘい！
Hey!
腑抜けた心に I need you
I need you in my gutless heart
噂のアルカロイド
A rumored alkaloid
あだなはネットの髑髏
My nickname is the net's skull
かき鳴らせディストーション
Let the distortion ring out
付け焼き刃の音
The sound of a makeshift blade
「1, 2, 3, fakkyu」
(1, 2, 3, f*ck you)
行き場を失くしたまま 踊り狂って
Lost and without a place to go, I dance like mad
惨々、笑われたって 死にはしない
No matter how much they laugh at my misery, I won't die
あーだこーだ言わんで 欲しい
I want you to stop with the 'this and that'
僕の心はエゴロック
My heart is an Ego Rock
斜め四十五度、ナンセンス
Forty-five degrees diagonal, nonsense
ノウハウかじって
Biting into the know-how
マンネリを明日に バイバイバイ
And saying bye-bye-bye to the rut of tomorrow
媚びへつらうその姿
That fawning attitude of yours
吐き気の空模様
Makes the sky look nauseating
シニカルな視線の雨
A rain of cynical stares
今日も両目を塞ぐふり
Today I'll pretend to cover my eyes again
僕の心はエゴロック
My heart is an Ego Rock
斜め四十五度、ナンセンス
Forty-five degrees diagonal, nonsense
ノウハウかじって
Biting into the know-how
マンネリを明日に バイバイバイ
And saying bye-bye-bye to the rut of tomorrow